It only takes a little over 2 hours to
reach Kinosaki [music] Onsen by train
from Kyoto Station. This makes Kinosaki
the perfect day trip or overnight escape
from the city. Kinosaki is a small and
charming Onsen town loved for its
traditional and relaxed atmosphere.
Begin with a walk along the Otani River
that runs through the center [music] of
the town. Easily the most picturesque
area, especially with the willow trees
lining the [music] canal. One of the
main attractions of Kinosaki is the
famous seven public bathhouses, [music]
all of which are tattoo friendly, making
it welcoming for foreign visitors.
If you prefer something more private,
you can also book a private Onsen and
have the space all to yourself.
If you decide [music] to stay overnight,
consider checking in to a traditional
Japanese inn and try a Kaiseki dinner, a
beautifully prepared multi-course
Japanese meal.
>> [music]
>> If that feels a bit too formal, you can
always sample the town's local
delicacies, including Tajima beef
and Matsuba snow crab.
For something a little different,
[music] try Onsen Tamago, eggs slowly
cooked in natural hot spring water.
Finally, hop on the Kinosaki Ropeway
[music] to the top and take in views of
the entire town from above. Small tip,
do this on a clear day, which we clearly
didn't.